

Gian Sonia Backend Developer

- **Q** 082321634181
- giansonia555@gmail.com
- Kota Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

SUMMARY

With three years of dedicated experience as a Backend Developer, I have a successful track record of completing major projects, including the creation of motor showroom websites for leading clients. I am ready to bring this expertise and experience to create innovative and captivating solutions for your company

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer Full Stack Developer

09/2023 - Present

Online School

- · Creating a website for the academic needs of SMP Persis Gandok.
- The required systems to be developed include an attendance system, a billing payment system, and a Computer Based Test (CBT) system.

Freelancer Fullstack Developer

04/2023 - 06/2023

SISMAC (Sistem Informasi Mandiri Utama Finance Community)

- Developing websites for each showroom in collaboration with Mandiri Utama Finance.
- · Analyzing the challenges and opportunities present in one of the showrooms.
- Creating a tailored system that aligns with the specific requirements of that showroom.
- · Building the system with the assistance of the Laravel framework and MySQL

EDUCATION

Teknik Informatika 05/2023 - Present

Universitas Perjuangan Tasikmalaya

SKILLS

CSS Intermediate MySql Intermediate
HTML Advanced Javascript Intermediate
Codelgniter Intermediate PHP Advanced

Laravel Advanced